# David **Brockbank**

Software Engineer

# **ABOUT**

Graduate software engineer with a year professional experience in the software development industry. Enjoyer of collaborative problem solving, experienced in Java, C#, Javascript, React, Python, and SQL. Projects done with C, C++, Python, and Java. CAD and electronic hobbyist.

# EXPERIENCE

## **Software Implementation Consultant**

Fast Enterprises · Full-time

Nov 2023 - Jun 2024 · 8 mos

Development and consulting for Inland Revenue's tax software. Worked with non-technical client to discuss issues and requirements. Implemented features and fixes in C#, .NET, and SQL, worked closely with domain specialists to extensively test before releasing to production. Evaluated potential features against system capabilities and clearly communicated them to the client.

## **Software Engineer Intern**

MTF Finance · Internship

Sep 2023 - Nov 2023 · 3 mos

Researched potential technologies to be used for an upgrade of internal lending software. Used C#, .NET, and SQL for main technology stack but researched Python, Django, and Vue.

#### **Computer Science Demonstrator**

University of Otago · Part-time

Feb 2023 - Jun 2023 • 5 mos

Guided students completing lab work for COSC202 - Software Development. Most of the work was in Java.

## Software developer

Iris Data Science · Internship

Dec 2022 - Mar 2023 • 4 mos

Design and development on a agricultural farming PWA for Agriganics in Javascript, React, and SQL. Implemented extensive offline capabilities, workflow design, and front-end development. Focus on defining, creating, and refining user experience on mobile and desktop environments.

## **Digital Archiver**

**Thames Treasury** · Volunteer

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020 · 3 mos

Digitized historical records and photographs relevant to the Thames-Coromandel area.

### Plasterer, Labourer

## **S & M Property Management Limited · Casual**

Nov 2016 - Dec 2022 • 6 yrs, 2 mos

Installing electric fencing, building frames, concrete pouring, painting, and plastering. Occasional leadings of small teams. Full-time during summers, part-time during school.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Science**

**University of Otago** 

Major in Computer Science, Minor in Energy Management GPA: 8.3/9.0 (A)

### **AWARDS**

Stephen Bowater Memorial Scholarship University of Otago 150th Entrance Scholarship University of Otago Scholarship in Science